Baker Prescott

Senior Frontend Developer

- AUSTIN, TX 78748 # 10 Dec 1990 +1 512 782 4477
- ▶ https://bakerprescott.netlify.app/ ♠ https://github.com/minionhub
 - in https://www.linkedin.com/in/baker-prescott-3b32b4277/
 - minionhub.dev#6550 🔀 bakerprescott007@gmail.com

PROFILE

Bringing more than 12 years of experience leading website design projects, including gathering user requirements, producing code, creating mockups and enhancing designs. Focused on creating clean, robust code with exceptional security. Achieves compatibility targets while meeting and exceeding customer demands.

SKILLS

Frontend

TRUSTLE

Svelte, ReactJS, AngularJS, VueJS, React Native, NextJS, NuxtJS, React Native, TailwindCSS, Qwik, JQuery

Content Management System

WordPress, Shopify, Strapi, Craft

Database Management Systems

MySQL, MongoDB, SQL Server

Backend

NodeJS, ExpressJS, Laravel, PHP, Java, Python, Firebase, GarphQL, RESTful API, Webpack, Ruby on Rails

Version Control Tools

Git(Github, Gitlab), SVN

DevOps

AWS, Docker, Kubernetes

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Engineer

Walnut Creek, United States

Jul 2020 - Mar 2023

Led a team of 5 developers in delivering several high-visibility projects, including large-scale applications using Next.js, AngularJS, Nuxt.js, Node/ExpressJS, Laravel, MySQL, and MongoDB from scratch resulting in a 20% increase in application productivity.

GOTZSYS

Jul 2017 – Jun 2020

Senior Full Stack Engineer

Porto Alegre, Brazil

- Developed and maintained e-commerce & healthcare products using React, NodeJS, MySQL, and MongoDB.
- Worked in Agile methodologies for development to deliver better applications and used Jira and Git as version control and tracking units.

DEVNOLOGY

Jul 2014 - Jun 2017

Software Developer

Belo Horizonte, Brazil

- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX, and JSON coding and coded websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery languages.
- Provided front-end website development using WordPress, Shopify, and other editing software.

Freelancer

Oct 2011 - Jun 2014

Software Developer



EDUCATION

State University of Santa Cruz

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science / Computer Science

Apr 2007 - Sep 2011 Ilhéus, Brazil